前情提要
趴下! 所有人趴下!
Down! Everybody down!
解放组织洗劫那些保险柜
Liber8 is fishing for something specific
是为了寻找一样特别的东西
in those safety deposit boxes.
怎么回事?
What's happening?
首先 我打赌这是一个全新的战斗策略
First, I bet a whole new battle strategy.
一年来你一直秘密使用这张SIM卡?
You used the same secret SIM card for a year?
解放组织给我下了套...
Liber8 wanted me on the hook and...
省省吧 贝蒂
Save it, Betty.
我们要拿你做诱饵
We're going to use you as bait.
你真觉得他们肯乖乖的把你捧作
Did you really think they were gonna let you play Steve Jobs
史蒂夫·乔布斯吗?
without a fight?
你得跟他们硬碰硬才行
You need a shark to take on these sharks.
离艾力克远一点
Stay away from Alec.
哪一个艾力克?
Which one?
我猜咱们两个是没法做朋友了 对吗?
So I guess we're not gonna be pals then, huh?
我也这样想
I don't see how.
别忘记做作业 帝奥
Don't forget to do your homework, Tio.
妈妈 我讨厌算分数
Mom, I hate fractions.
我也是 但你不练习考试就会不及格
So did I, but you won't pass your exams without them.
帝奥 我不是叫你把门关上了吗?
Tio, I thought I told you to close the door?
爹地!
Daddy!
嘿!
Hey!
我想死你了!
I missed you so much!
你去哪儿了?
Where have you been?
我的生日你都错过了
You missed my birthday.
我也不想的 宝贝
I didn't want to, baby.
嘿!
Hey!
爹地不应该回来的
Daddy knows he shouldn't be here.
我们说过的安全第一
We talked about staying safe.
我另有办法
I have another way.
去玩吧 去
Go play. Go.
她的DNA是伪造的
Her DNA is forged.
万一被发现是你这种人的女儿...
If they find out that she's the daughter of a..
哪种人? 逃亡者?
A fugitive?
恐怖分子?
A terrorist?
你不会真的相信吧
You don't believe that.
我怎么想又没有用
It doesn't matter what I believe.
当我无比渴望跟你们相聚的时候
Belief is the only thing that keeps me going
信念是唯一支撑我走下去的力量
when I'm dying to be with you both.
我是说 帝奥需要知道信念是...
I mean, Tio needs to learn that belief is...
当你偷听别人说话时信念就会是个问题!
belief is only a problem when you're eavesdropping!
让你尝尝我的厉害!
Because this is what happens!
去右边!!!
To the right!!
右边!!!
On the right!!!
进去 进去!!!
In, in, in!!!!
那边有人
There.
搜查完毕
Clear.
没有发现 长官
All clear sir.
这儿仍然残留着他的信息素
His pheromone levels are still ambient.
为了自己着想 你们两个说实话吧
It's better for the both of you if you were to tell the truth.
你们跟他有什么关系?
What's your connection to him?
你搞错了
Please.
他刚刚还威胁要杀了我们
He threatened to kill us.
我们都是好公民
We're good citizens.
忠于国家
We're loyal.
那你呢 小甜心?
And what about you, sweetheart?
你忠于企业集团议会吗?
Are you loyal to the corporate congress?
我已经在学校立过誓言了
I took the oath in school.
你不希望妈妈有麻烦吧 对不对?
You want to help your mother out, don't you?
那就说实话 他去哪儿了?
So tell me, where did he go?
贝尔塔 下来吧
Verta, down.
立刻
Now.
瞄准他了!
I got him!
下来
Get down.
快点下来!!!
Get down now!!!
慢点
Easy.
跪下!
Down on your knees!
超越时间线 第三季第五集 三十分钟直播
照片标签上就写
Hash-tag
"亲我的屁屁 弗门塔斯"怎么样?
"kiss my ass Fermitas"?
经典!
Epic!
弗门塔斯 助纣为虐
这公司的保安干什么吃的
The corporate security was primitive at best.
那些抗议者应该连大厅
Those protesters never should have made it
都进不去才对
past the lobby.
他们为什么瞄准弗门塔斯?
Why paint a bullseye on Fermitas?
你的用词还真是讽刺啊
Well, that's an ironic choice of words.
弗门塔斯是世界上最大的军火制造商之一
Fermitas is one of the world's largest weapons manufacturers,
就像军火界的沃尔玛
like the Wal-Mart for warlords.
你在跟这个案子吗?
You chasing this one down?
非法入室和示威抗议?
Trespassing and opinionated protests?
还真不是我的工作范围
It's not really my department.
在我看来是解放组织的煽动行为
It seems to me like Liber8's recruiting methods
终于起作用了
are paying off.
非暴力抗议早在你的朋友
Civil disobedience has been around
出现之前就有了
long before your friends showed up.
卡洛斯?
Carlos?
我们都是长途跋涉走到今天
We've both travelled long distances,
见过很多他人闻所未闻的事情
seen things other people can't know or understand.
我们可以互相帮助
We could help each other.
我们已经是一路人马了 你还想怎样?
We're already on the same team, what more do you want?
每个人都需要伙伴
Everyone needs a partner.
卡洛斯和艾力克...
Carlos, Alec...
你们的友谊正在分崩离析
Those relationships are fracturing.
凯瑟琳知道你来找我吗?
Does Katherine know you're here?
是她要我关照你的
She asked me to keep an eye on you.
这可算不上是个回答
That is not an answer.
也许他只是在向你表示善意
It's possible his offer was a gesture of goodwill.
他的字典里可没有"善意"这个词
Goodwill is not in his arsenal.
我不信任他
I don't trust him.
他知道我敬重你 也知道我们有交流
Well, he knows I respect you and he knows we talk,
也许他的动机就是这么简单
so maybe that's all it is.
但你能告诉我这些我很感激
I appreciate you telling me, though.
这里的大部分人都没有家人
Most of the people in this cell don't have families.
他们在传统社会中没有立足之地
They found themselves lost in traditional society.
其中一些是我从街上收进来的
Some I recruited off the streets,
其他的则是主动投奔而来
others found their way to me.
他们中的很多人都缺乏母爱
For many of them, mother-less.
我填补了这个角色
I can fulfil that roll.
你对当前的局势怎么看?
How do things feel to you?
解放组织自从银行抢劫案之后就悄无声息
Liber8 has been quiet since the bank robberies.
各方势力也没有动静
All that energy in theatre to little or no effect.
你也有这样的感觉?
You feel that?
某种程度上是的
In a way.
你不也是吗?
Don't you?
那里面是什么?
What's in there?
很高兴你来了
I'm glad you're here.
好吧 如果我不接
Okay, if I don't answer this,
卢卡斯会起疑心的
Lucas is going to wonder why.
你觉得我会蠢到让你给他
You think I'm gonna let you send him some kind of message
通风报信吗?
by the way you answer?
不许接
No.
我会按你们的要求接电话
I will answer it any way you want.
他不常打电话给我的
He doesn't call that often.
我说过了不行
I said no.
如果她是对的怎么办?
What if she's right?
我们来决定什么时候拿她当诱饵
We'll pick the moment to use her to our advantage.
按我们的方式
On our terms.
嘿 你去哪儿了?
Hey, where've you been?
碰到了一个老朋友
I ran into an old friend.
有意思 我都不知道你还有老朋友
Funny, I wasn't aware you had any of those.
怎么回事?
What is it?
这个地方从来都不能消停一下
This department just can't catch a break.
强行入室罪
Break and enter.
非法侵入罪
Criminal trespass.
怠忽致危罪
Reckless endangerment.
直接叫我恐怖分子好了
Just call me a terrorist.
反正在你眼里都是一个样
That's what we all are to you.
当着两位证人
This is being recorded
卡梅伦探员和福乃格探长的面
in front of two witnesses,
以下对话将记录在案
Agent Cameron and Detective Fonnegra.
我确定你刚才的话只是讽刺 无其他含义
I will stipulate that you were being sarcastic just then.
视网膜扫描 心跳正常
不要再犯这样的错误
Don't repeat that mistake.
接下来 继续记录再案
Now, for the record,
你已经了解了你的权利
you've already been advised of your rights.
我们的行为是无害的
What we did was harmless.
没有人受伤
Nobody got hurt.
你的所作所为已经够得上起诉了
What you did is an indictable offense!
那是要坐牢的
You could serve time.
现在我想知道为什么
Now I want to know why.
狮门大学被血洗之后
Do I really have to say it
原因不是显而易见吗?
after the bloodbath at LGU?
我是在表明立场
I'm taking a stand.
那次射杀 还有之后你的做法...
That shooting, your tactics...
用于应对威胁是必要 且适度的
Were necessary and proportionate to the threat.
告诉我你要请律师
Tell me you want a lawyer.
不是吧 老爸
You can't be serious, dad.
克里斯汀 我只能帮你到这儿了
Christine, this is as far as I am willing to stretch.
现在 快说
Now, say the words.
给我找个律师
I want a lawyer.
好吧 刚才那一幕我们可没有办法完全
Well, we're not going to be able to sweep that one
隐瞒过去
under the rug.
如果她免于被起诉的话 他和整个部门都会被
If she isn't charged, it puts him and the whole department
都将被推上风口浪尖
under a microscope.
这又不是她一个人做的
She didn't do this on her own.
哦 没错啊 他们都有罪哦
Oh yeah, sure, they're both guilty.
但是其他孩子不会上头条
But that other kid's not gonna lead the news.
他们才会
They are.
不管怎么运作 这都是一个两败俱伤的结果
This is lose-lose any way you play it.
我觉得你还少说了一个
I think you're one "lose" short.
我是不是需要个工会代表?
Do I need my union rep?
这又不是在审问你 杰克
There's no inquisition here, Jack.
是还没...
Yet...
你女儿支持解放组织
You're daughter is pro Liber8.
你认为这事会怎样?
How do you think that looks?
听你的意思 是不是又要逼我辞职了?
Is this the part where I clear out my desk again?
我监督你的工作
Just because I'm your oversight
并不代表我不支持你的工作
doesn't mean I'm not your advocate.
你知道是谁在资助我
You know who I'm funded by.
很了解
Intimately.
那你就应该清楚我这次可没有那么容易就被挤走
Then you realize I won't be removed as easily as last time.
在这件事儿上 我们有可以合作的空间
I think that there's room for cooperation.
我们互利互惠嘛
Every back needs scratching.
你现在有什么主意吗?
What did you have in mind?
引导舆论
Spin.
这事儿我帮不了她
I can't save her from this.
不行?
Can't?
让别的部门来处理
Kick it over to another department.
让特里来做
Let Terry handle it.
他欠你的
He owes you.
或者布拉特 那次你放他儿子回家
Or Brett, for that time you took his son home
没有带回警署
instead of the precinct.
她肯定会上头条的 尼基
She's gonna lead the news, Niky.
我所能做的就是把她和其他孩子一样看待
The only thing I can do is treat her like any other kid.
那不一样!
She's not!
必须这样
She has to be.
你会毁了她的未来的
This will destroy her future.
是她自己的选择
She made a choice.
五年前你也是如此
Same way you did five years ago.
我们要聊的不是这个!
That is not what we're talking about!
你知道吗 以前的你是认可我的原则的
You know, there was a time when you believed in my principles.
那时候的你还相信原则的
There was a time you believed in them, too.
我现在也是
I still do.
克里斯必将被追究责任的
Chrissy will be held accountable.
现在到了这一步
While we're at it,
我想要创建一个二阶认证协议
I'd like to create a two-stage authentication protocol
以便于日后有任何变动
for any future changes.
好的 我可以等
Sure, I can hold.
赛德科技 重新设置主密码?
哦 真是摇身一变啊
Oh, wardrobe upgrade I see.
帅啊
Sharp.
提升自我呗
I'm evolving.
董事会的事情处理的不赖 小伙子
You did great with that board, kid.
你独自一人和罪恶进行抗争
You held your own against the vipers.
现在你需要找一个正义的小伙伴
Now you need to bring in a mongoose.
上次你还用鲨鱼做比来着
Last time it was a shark.
随意啦
Whatever.
找一个可以为了你而战斗的伙伴
Someone who can strike on your behalf.
要是你想选我的话...
If that happens to be me...
那个 这个事儿吧
Uh, well, the thing is,
既然现在和董事会那边没什么纷争了
while things settle down with the board,
我们也就不要再招聘什么人了
we're in a bit of a hiring freeze.
现在...
Now...
你可不要忘了是我不就之前把你从零售店的
You may remember I rescued you from a menial job
粗活儿里解救出来的
at a retail store not too long ago.
我让你重新回归正轨
I gave you back your destiny.
我们说好了的
We had a deal.
你这样可不对啊
And this wasn't it.
哦 歇歇吧
Oh, come on.
你还可以再找到一个可以利用的技术宅男的
You'll find another tech-savy kid to profit by.
我不是独一无二的 你我都心知肚明
We both know that I'm not unique.
你在逗我?
You're kidding me?
你他妈的可是能创造未来的人啊
You're the damn architect of the future.
按照目前赛德科技发展来看
As far as Sadtech goes,
我为你准备好了一份合理的赔偿
I'm prepared to offer you a reasonable settlement.
你准备好了
You're prepared.
你还真是准备好了
You're prepared!
你是个不错的老师
You were a good teacher.
哦
Whooo.
哦 这可不能就这么算了
Oh, this is not how it ends.
好吧 你有别的方案再来找我
Well, let me know when you find an alternative.
你最近在读那本关于管理的书
You've been reading that book on management.
叫什么来着
What's the name?
我没有...
I haven't...
"沉默的力量"...
The "power in silence"...
不提出质疑 只陈述看法
No, no questions where a statement will do,
用法律手段制裁你的敌人
roll over your enemies with legal power.
见鬼 你知道那个作者
Hell, you know the author.
我不认识
I don't.
你就是那个作者
It's you, kid.
就是你
It's you.
感谢你们部门能提供给我们这次机会
I'm glad your department offered me this opportunity.
你是实权人物 我们节目确实需要更多你这样的人
You're a take-charge guy and we definitely need more of those,
尤其是现在市长更替如此频繁的情况下
especially with our revolving door of mayors.
最近简直就像七个小矮人轮番上场一样
It's like the seven dwarfs lately.
同感 开心果和糊涂蛋已经完蛋了
Yeah, happy and dopey are dead,
我觉得现在台上的是爱生气
I think grumpy's in charge now.
有趣的说法 这是个亮点
Funny, that's a bonus.
别太担心 我们不会咄咄逼人
And don't worry, we'll go easy.
我看过你的节目 博尔顿小姐
I've seen your show, miss Bolton.
你从来都是咄咄逼人
You don't do easy.
别让奈杰尔打乱你的思路
Don't let Nigel interrupt you,
他有时候是很难容忍
he can be insufferable at times.
但制片人说 我不能老是孤立他
But my producer says I have to stop cutting him off so much
因为...其实我也不懂
because... I don't know.
男权社会吧
The patriarchy.
奈杰尔我应付得了
I'm sure I can handle Nigel.
我就是喜欢警察的这个范儿
I do love cops.
观点交锋
您将不会把您的女儿和其他孩子区别对待
Your daughter will be treated just like any other kid.
奈杰尔 你觉得这可能吗?
Nigel, can you believe this?
当然不可能了
No, absolutely not.
狄龙警官只有对企业集团的大佬们
Inspector Dillon is answerable
才会表现出负责的态度
only to his corporate overlords,
他才不会对公民 对这座城市负责
certainly not the people and not the city.
现在的问题是我的女儿需要对谁负责
This is about who my daughter answers to.
她的行为很严重 一定会被起诉
It's a serious offense and she will be held accountable.
是初犯吧?
A first offense?
换做任何一个父母都会想方设法
Any parent can understand wanting to use whatever
利用任何可能...
influence they could...
戴安娜 我不像普通家长
Diana, I don't get to be any parent.
我的责任是二十四小时全天候的
My accountability is 24/7.
而且 很不幸 对我女儿来讲 由于血缘关系
And, unfortunately for my daughter, by association,
她的也是
hers is too.
在你的职责之下已经出现过丑闻 警方掩盖真相
Under your accountability we've had scandals, police cover-ups
两位市长身亡这样的事情
and two dead mayors.
警长 你说说看
Inspector, tell us:
如果你不是警察 你女儿现在的情况
How would your daughter's situation
会出现多大的改观吗?
play out different if you weren't a cop?
如果我不是警察?
If I wasn't a cop?
那就没什么可讲的了 对吧?
There wouldn't be a story, would there?
所以你打算将为非作歹的女儿
So you're gonna let the system
直接移交司法部门处理?
take care of your miscreant daughter?
法律系统就是这样运作的 没错
That's how the justice system works, yes.
那这是否也适用于你的私人警备枪杀
Does that include your own private police
无辜的大学生呢?
shooting innocent university students?
你现在竟然还没下台
And you're still in charge.
如果我们不让这样的
If we can't remove
所谓的管理者下台的话 戴安娜
our so-called leaders, Diana,
就是放任法西斯主义
we're staring fascism in the face.
您是法西斯吗 长官?
Are you a fascist, inspector?
在奈杰尔的眼中 我就是个公司的走狗而已
According to Nigel, I'm a corporate lackey.
但我觉得这两种形象有点矛盾
It seems contradictory to me.
问得好
Excellent question.
比平时有进步啊
That was better than usual.
切断信号
Kill the feed.
他们堵住了大门 在门上安了炸药
They blocked and booby-trapped the doors.
大部分员工都被赶出来了
Most of the staff were forced out
里面还有狄龙局长和其他八个人质
except for inspector Dillon and eight other hostages.
有几个解放组织的成员?
How many Liber8?
不清楚 不过有人认出了特拉维斯·贝尔塔
Unknown, but witnesses identified both Travis Verta
和卢卡斯·英格拉姆
and Lucas Ingram.
好的
ok.
我们先想办法跟他们谈判吧
We try and talk them out first.
同时 再计划下应该怎么进去
In the meantime, get us an entry plan.
要进去很简单 但是他们一定知道
Easy enough to get in, but they had to know
想要出来几乎是不可能
it would be virtually impossible to get out.
你的内线最近很安静啊
Your contact's gone quiet.
没有她我们能行吗?
Can we still do this without her?
别担心 我会有办法的
Trust me, I'll find a way.
其实我们都知道现在的状况
We know how this plays.
你们的人在外面一边封锁街道
Your troops are outside shutting down streets,
一边想方设法找其他的入口
searching for entries into the building from above and below.
你在每个入口都安装了炸弹
You've wired all entries to blow,
你早就盘算好了谈判条件
you've got a list of demands,
你也知道我们是不会搭理你的
you know we're not gonna meet them.
如果外面是福乃格在负责的话
And, if your boy Fonnegra is in charge,
他会知道 我们来不是为了抢一大笔钱
he knows we're not in this to steal a million
然后逃到玻利维亚去的
and fly off to Bolivia.
那你想要什么?
So what is it you want?
很快你就会知道了
You're about to find out.
哪位
Yes.
取款遭拒 请联络当地银行
是他
It's him.
我什么时候变的这么混蛋了?
When did I become such a dick?
别开玩笑
It's not a joke.
我没开玩笑
I'm not joking.
但是...
But he's still...
你就是他 他就是你
You're him, he's you.
他怎么可以这么狠?
How can he be so vindictive?
你就不会这样
I don't see that in you.
我成功穿越时空
I travelled through time, win.
也成功赢得心爱的女孩 他有理由恨我
I got the girl, win.
你失去了你的爸爸
You lost your father.
对 但是我不像另一个我反应那么大
Yeah, but I'm not like the other me there.
我见过艾舍尔 我一点也不喜欢他
I met the guy, I didn't like him.
不管怎么说 艾舍尔还是你爸爸
Escher was still your father.
没法父子相认 总会有些遗憾
There's gotta be some regret not knowing him.
遗憾什么的以后再说吧
I'll try on some regret later.
现在我们没空管这事
Right now we've got other problems.
在他们杀害人质前
Ok, we've got 30 minutes to give them access
我们还有三十分钟的时间
to the station's satellite network
为他们拿到卫星代码
before they start killing hostages.
他还想来一次直播演讲
And he wants to make a public address.
这没道理啊
It doesn't make sense.
过去 当卡加梅和卢卡斯想要宣传他们的理念
In the past, when Kagame and Lucas wanted to reach people
他们会直接黑电脑
they simply hacked in.
为什么现在还要来玩挟持人质
Why take hostages and
这样会暴露自己的把戏?
expose themselves like this?
不知道
I don't know.
我们是不可能让他们做什么直播的
And we're never going to let them broadcast anything.
这里有个维护面板
There's a maintenance panel here
是通到排气管那里去的
that leads to the ventilation gangway.
我们可以派几个人进去
We could send in a small team,
为大部队进入打开通道
secure access for a larger force.
我们不是应该先谈判吗?
Shouldn't we start with negotiation?
特拉维斯是不会和你达成协议的
Travis is never gonna cut a deal.
我们可以先通过谈判把狄龙救出来
We negotiate for Dillon.
人质是不分三六九等的
There are no VIP's in a hostage situation.
如果是我在里面 狄龙在外面负责解救人质
If I was in there and Dillon was out here,
他会跟我做一样的决定的
he would make exactly the same call.
让电力公司伪造一个变压器故障
Have hydro stage a transformer failure,
告诉他们因为这个原因不能直播
tell them that's why they're off the air.
这个说法骗不了他们多长时间
It won't convince them for long.
我们也不需要多长时间
We don't need that long,
够你们找到入口就行了
just long enough for you to export this entry.
带两个人 摸清状况
Take two guys, see what you can find.
你也要进去
You're going in there also.
跟他们一起?
With them?
不
No.
用你的方式进去 好吗?
Do that thing that you do, ok?
随时保持联系
Keep a line open for me.
琪拉
Kiera.
我们要救的是所有的人质
We want to rescue all of them.
知道了
I know.
现在有两个人已经...
We have a two man team...
看来好戏已经开始了
They're starting to play their games.
没事 我临时找了个备用电源
It doesn't matter, I rigged a back-up circuit.
马上就好 三 二 一
It should activate in three... two... one.
在我们得到卫星系统的代码之前
It's the only magic trick I've got
我只能做到这一步了
until we get those satellite codes.
今天对你来说真的很忙啊
Busy day for you.
逮捕你自己的女儿 在电视节目上道貌岸然
Arrest your own daughter, act the righteous man on TV,
现在又被当人质给抓起来了
get taken hostage.
晚上的运气有点不好
Tonight can only be a let down.
你到底想要什么?
What do you want?
你觉得我想要什么?
What do you think I want?
你一直想抓住我
You've been chasing me long enough.
你喜欢扯一大堆解放人民的鬼话
You know, you talk a great game about freeing the people,
但一到你身上
but it's on your terms.
要是有人跟你意见不合...
Anybody who doesn't agree with you...
就会被老爸抓起来
Ends up being arrested by daddy.
你当不了英雄 局长
You're not that guy, inspector.
你拿不到那把枪的 也无法扭转局势
You're not getting the gun, you're not saving the day.
看来你很自信啊?
Pretty confident in that, are you?
我是很自信
I am.
很好
Great.
福乃格最好能给我想要的东西
Your boy Fonnegra better get me what I want.
我十分赞同你的想法 贝尔塔先生
I'm in agreement with your principles, Mr. Verta.
要限制正在增长的公司企业的权力
Strip the power away from this growing corporate mono-culture.
闭嘴  奈杰尔 别乱说话
Shut up, Nigel, you're encouraging a terrorist!
只有解放组织看清了 如果我们不反抗
Liber8 has the only clear vision of what lies ahead
未来的下场会怎样
if we don't speak up.
贝尔塔先生和他的朋友们
Mr. Verta and his friends here
就是未来唯一的希望
are the only hope for the future.
别再乱说话
No more talking heads.
别担心 死不了
Oh, he'll live.
还能坚持一会儿
For a while.
你们肯定很想去帮他止血吧
You might want to block up that hole.
你别动
Not you.
当我看你的节目的时候
When I watch your show,
我真为你感到羞愧
I'm ashamed for you.
为你的观众感到羞愧
For all your viewers.
没有思想 没有分析
No awareness, no analysis,
有的只是些翻动言论
just reactionary opinions.
节目做成这样 你也有责任
You are part of the problem.
不过你只是一个漂亮的傀儡罢了
A pretty, empty puppet.
只会带着一群人嬉笑作乐
Leading everyone on a merry dance.
告诉福乃格他没有多少时间了
Tell Fonnegra he doesn't have much time.
特拉维斯?
Travis?
所有人质都还活着吗?
Are all the hostages still alive?
是的 但是时间不多了
For now, but the clock is ticking.
十五分钟之内给我接通卫星服务
Full access to those satellites in 15 minutes
不然我就杀了博尔顿小姐 表明下我的决心
or I'll shoot Miss Bolton next as a sign of my resolve.
特拉维斯 我们在解决你代码的事
Travis, we're working on getting you the codes,
但是这需要一点时间
but it's slow going.
公司不愿意交出代码
The company doesn't want to give them up.
别跟我来谈判这一套 福乃格
Save the negotiator clich, Fonnegra.
拖延战术只会导致
Stalling is only going to lead to something...
无法挽回的结果
Terminal.
喂
Yeah.
我进来了
I'm in.
很好
Alright, good.
随时跟我联系
Keep me apprise step by step.
知道了
Roger that.
我想我知道为什么电视台
I think I know why the network
不把卫星交出来
isn't releasing access to the satellites.
2010年整个公司已经被弗门塔斯公司买下了
That whole conglomerate was bought out in 2010 by Fermitas.
第一频道被军火商买下了?
The weapons-maker owns Channel 1?
戴安娜·博尔顿几年前曾经
Diana Bolton ran a huge expose on Fermitas
要曝光弗门塔斯的内幕
a couple years ago.
弗门塔斯声称要控告她
Fermitas announced an intention to sue,
之后又不告了
then dropped the suit.
人们当时以为是因为赢不了
People figured it was because it wasn't winnable,
但是事实是
but really...
如果你不能封锁媒体 就把它们买下来
If you can't muzzle the press, you buy them.
将其私下收购
Private acquisition.
私下收购?
Private acquisition?
这么说没人知道?
So nobody knows?
卢卡斯也许知道了
Lucas might have found out.
是吗?
Did he?
不是我告诉他的 我发誓
Not from me, I swear it.
你现在在哪呢?
What's your twenty?
监控室 看特拉维斯和卢卡斯在楼里扫荡呢
Security room, watching Travis and Lucas storm the castle.
所有这一切就为了在电视上播出他们的宣言?
All this effort to broadcast a manifesto?
嗯 这还有条爆炸新闻等着你呢
Well, here's some breaking news for ya.
弗门塔斯是这家电视台的幕后老板
Fermitas owns the station.
私人收购买卖
Private buying private.
那些保险箱
The safety deposit boxes.
解放组织就是这么发现这笔交易的
That's how Liber8 found out about the sale.
加尔萨和索尼娅不在
Garza and Sonya aren't here.
什么 兵分两路 分头进攻?
What, two-prong attack?
有道理
Makes sense.
卡洛斯?
Carlos?
保持联系
Stay in touch.
我们遇到问题了
We have a problem.
我的人已经进去了但是到演播室的
My men are inside but access to the studio
门被装上了炸药
is rigged with explosives.
拆弹小组呢?
Bomb squad?
我们从来没见过这种东西
We've never seen anything like this.
长官 企业集团代表来了
Sir, the corporate rep is here.
稍等我一下
Give me a second.
你是本尼迪克特?
You Benedict?
是的
Yes.
弗门塔斯的?
Fermitas?
是的
Yes.
太好了
Good.
他们已经枪伤了一人除非我们能满足
One man has been shot and there will be others
解放组织的部分要求 否则其他人也有危险了
unless we give Liber8 at least part of what they demanded.
恐怖组织想要连接电视台卫星的代码
Terrorists want the codes to the station's satellite.
抱歉 警探 但是公司有着严格的规定
Detective, I'm sorry, that company has a strict policy
禁止和恐怖分子谈判
against negotiating with terrorists.
所以你非常高兴能成为谋杀犯的帮凶?
So you're perfectly content with being accomplices to murder?
这家电视台也是弗门塔斯的 是不是?
That is Fermitas's business, isn't it?
我不想浪费你的时间
I don't want to waste your time.
解放组织至少拿到了弗门塔斯的一个保险箱
Liber8 emptied at least one Fermitas safety deposit box.
这也许是你们把里面的情报
This could be an opportunity
拿回来的好机会
for you to retrieve that information.
否则 不论里面是什么
Otherwise, Liber8 still has
东西依然掌握在解放组织手里
whatever it is that you lost,
而他们会好好利用的
and they will use it.
就好像在下鱼饵一样
It's like baiting a hook.
是啊 我们有麻烦了 他们不会善罢甘休的
Yeah, we got a problem, they're not gonna go for it.
把我留下放其他人走
You keep me as collateral and everybody else walks.
锁定目标
不可能
No deal.
局长 你觉得接下来会怎样?
What do you think happens next, inspector?
特拉维斯 出什么事情了?
What's happening, Travis?
不是什么好事
Nothing good.
卫星
The satellite.
你可以用了
You have access.
转发器的代码正在发给你
Transponder codes are being fed to you now.
谎言中的又一天
Live to lie another day.
你没事吧?
You ok?
不 我感觉很不好
No, I'm not.
我甚至在为奈杰尔感到难过
I even feel badly for Nigel.
所以我知道我现在糟糕透了
That's how I know I'm a wreck.
好了
Good to go.
重新设置卫星需要二十分钟
Re-tasking the satellite will take 20 minutes.
准备直播 三 二 ...
We're live in three... Two...
你们中的很多人觉得认识我
Most of you think you know me.
特拉维斯·贝尔塔
Travis Verta.
解放组织
Liber8.
杀人犯
Killer.
恐怖分子
Terrorist.
疯子
Lunatic.
现我又在这打断你们的节目
And now here I am, interrupting your programming.
这样的节目必须被打断
That's some programming that needs to be interrupted.
我们过去拥有的公司 现在拥有了我们
Companies we used to own, own us.
以前我们选出的政府 现在被收买
Governments that used to be voted in, are bought.
而可以用来曝光这些的
And a supposedly "free press"
所谓自由媒体
who could expose all this
现在都被这些企业集团所拥有
are now owned by these very corporations.
我们孩子们的自由生活岌岌可危
Our children's lives are at stake.
未来即将到来
The future is coming.
而他们只被要求做一件事
It wants only one thing from them:
就是绝对服从
Obedience.
看起来不太好啊
That doesn't look good.
是不妙
It's not.
卢卡斯在里面加入了2077年才有的一些成分
Lucas added some 2077 into the equation.
炸药
艾力克 你的出现刚刚好
Alec, your timing couldn't be better.
能用赛德科技的服务器搜索一下简单爆炸装置
Can you have the Sadtech servers run an IED bomb search,
起爆电路...
firing schematics...
我现在在派朗的办公室里
I'm in my office at Piron.
哦 当然
Of course.
当然是了
Of course you are.
你以为我是另一个我 是吗?
You thought I was other me, didn't you?
你早就知道了
You knew.
我还希望你不知道
I was hoping you didn't,
不过你这样我一点都不惊讶
but I wish I was surprised.
艾力克 我需要保护你
Alec, I needed to protect you,
我以为这是最好的
and I thought this was the best...
每个人都在努力的保护我
Everyone's trying to protect me,
但是你是借保护我的名义
but you scratch that protection
暗中谋取自己的利益
and it's self-interest underneath.
艾力克 我相信你
Alec, I trust you.
我了解你
I know you.
另一个你背叛了我
The other one betrayed me.
怎么会?
How?
我想补偿你 我一定做到
I want to make it up to you, and I will.
但是现在 人命关天
But right now, people's lives are at stake.
我以为我们是朋友
I thought we were friends,
但是我想我们之间只是交易
but I guess we were just business.
但是也没关系 我现在对交易很在行
But that's ok, I'm learning a lot in business.
不
No.
不是的 艾力克我们之间从来不是交易
No, Alec, it was never business.
从来都不是
Never.
嗯 那现在是了
Well, it is now.
你知道 一旦你的搭档背叛了你
You know, once a partner betrays you
你只有两个选择
there's only two choices:
要不买断他们 要不断绝关系
Buy them out, or shut them down.
对不起
I'm sorry.
绿线
Green wire.
什么?
What?
再见 琪拉
Goodbye, Kiera.
不要 艾力克?
No, Alec?
艾力克?
Alec?
哇 别碰它
Woah, leave it alone.
这是什么?
What is it?
是我帮琪拉做的东西
It's just something I'm working on for Kiera.
我也想喝两杯
I could use one of those.
我以为你不喜欢喝威士忌
I thought whiskey wasn't your thing.
是的 自我提升中
Yeah, I'm evolving.
我感觉现在的场景似曾相识
I'm experiencing some profound dajavu .
不是吧?
Seriously?!
这瓶威士忌比你年纪都大呢
That scotch is older than you are.
怎么个似曾相识法?
Dajavu  how?
得了吧 孩子
Come on, kid.
坐在你面前的可是我啊
It's me.
我眼睛很好
My vision is better than 20/20.
即使在我看到两个你 也能看得清清楚楚
Even when I am seeing double.
你有什么计划吗?
Did you even have a plan?
从时间上来说
Chronologically speaking.
孩子 你可是个时间旅行者
You're a time-traveller, kid.
你的成就可以堪比攀登珠穆朗玛峰
You scaled Everest.
探索马里亚纳海沟
Explored the Marianas Trench.
这可是人类的一大步
One giant step for mankind.
一个勇敢的新世界 你做了这一切为什么?
A brave new world, and you did it all for what?
泡妞?
Pussy?
我从没期望你是个有同情心有内涵的人
I never expected you to have any empathy or decency.
那条时间线上不是 这条也不可能
Not on that timeline or on this one.
嗯 这也好 这样你就永远不会失望
Well, that's good because you'll never be disappointed.
不像我
Unlike me.
你记得我们曾经做过的苍穹项目吗?
You remember when we used to have arc?
密切的合作?
A functioning partnership?
美好的未来
A future?
你为了重头来过就毁了我的生活
This little do-over of yours ruined my life.
是的 也不是完全没有用
Yeah, well it hasn't been in vain.
没有人的生活会被毁掉
Nobody's life needs to be ruined.
就看你怎么做了
That just depends on what you're capable of.
孩子 谢谢你看得起我
Kid, I'm flattered.
但是你要对付的不止我一个
But I'm not the only one you're dancing with.
你还没看见艾米丽的本事呢
And you haven't even begun to see Emily's do-si-do.
他把代码给我们了
He gave us the codes.
这个代码会给她们卫星的部分控制权
The codes might allow for some control of the satellite,
但是不会向外或向地面传输信号
but not outbound communication or the downlink.
没有人会看到特拉维斯的广播
Nobody is gonna see Travis's broadcast.
如果他有所察觉
If he figures that out...
他会觉得我们在耍他
He'll think we played him.
你的代码完全没用
Your codes were bullshit,
但一旦出事 搭上的人名可是货真价实的
but the corpses of those innocent people will be real.
而这些都会算到你和你公司的头上
And that's on you and your company.
我们有自己的警力
We have private forces.
雇佣军
Mercenaries.
请让我们协助你们
Allow us to assist you.
绝不可能
That's never gonna happen.
有进展吗?
Any luck?
希望如此
I hope so.
好了 搞定了
Ok, it's neutralized.
应急反应部队待命
Standby for ERT.
让他们进去
Send them in.
一分钟之后我们需要转移下他们的注意力
We need a diversion in one minute.
传输错误 代码不完整
代码不完整
The codes are incomplete.
没有代码就没有第二阶段
There's no phase 2 without them.
你外面的朋友似乎觉得我在开玩笑
Your friends outside don't seem to think I'm serious.
我们来让他们清醒一下吧
Let's wake them up.
让他们都站起来 脸对着墙
Stand them all up, make them face the wall.
快点
Move it!
不要这样做
Don't do this.
已经做了
It's already done.
不许讲话
No talking.
给我卫星的全部代码
Full access to that satellite right now,
否则就准备开始收尸吧
or I start dropping bodies.
狄龙是第一个
Dillon's first.
机会就这一个
Now, or never.
让他们攻进去
Send them in!
一组 行动
Team one, go!
找到他们
Find them.
杀了他们
Kill them.
我在美国航空航天局的朋友帮我拿到了代码
My NASA source helped me hack the codes.
这样就可以完全掌控卫星数据的传输
It should allow for full data routing to the satellite.
贝蒂?
Betty?
我知道你可以联系到卢卡斯
I know you can get a hold of Lucas.
卡洛斯
Carlos...
把代码发给他 现在
Send him those codes, now.
否则他们就死定了
Or they all start dying.
目标被击毙
Tango down.
自己人
Friendlies.
两个自己人
You've got two friendlies here!
等等 我们的朋友发过来完整的代码
Wait! Our friends sent the full codes,
我可以进入部分系统了
I can get some system access now.
这不会是他们的又一个花招吧?
Is this another trick?
不是
No.
协议正确
Protocols are good,
卫星间的数据正在传输
up-linking between satellites.
加尔萨 可以了
Garza. You're clear.
我们走
Let's go.
我们有九十秒的时间 走!
We've got 90 seconds. Go!
二组 报告情况?
Team two sit-rep?
正在接近演播室
Closing on studio.
所有人都在不间断的被监视
Every one of us is under constant surveillance.
这意味着当政府或者像弗门塔斯这样的大公司
What that surveillance means is that our every utterance
认为我们给他们制造了麻烦时,这些监控视频
becomes part of a court case that can be used against us
将会被法庭采用
when the government, or a company like Fermitas,
作为控告我们的证据
decides we're too much trouble.
走!
Move!
直接进去
Straight through!!!
我们找到他们了
We got them.
这有四个
Four here.
把硬盘给我
Give me the drive!
加尔萨那有消息了吗?
Any word from Garza?
看来你是对的
It turns out you were right.
弗门塔斯一直在监视大多数的企业集团
Fermitas has been spying on most of the big corporations.
她已经拿到了存有大量间谍信息的硬盘
She's pulled a drive with a treasure trove of espionage
这样扳倒企业集团议会
that should make bringing down the corporate congress
就简单多了
much easier.
包括派朗?
Including Piron?
艾力克·赛德勒不会知道是怎么回事的
Alec Sadler won't know what hit him.
我就想听这个
That's what I like to hear.
你也会很高兴知道你的理念
You'll also be happy to know that your message
也通过电波传递出去了
made it onto the airwaves.
让我们祈祷有人在听吧
Let's hope someone's listening.
他看起来不太开心啊
He does not look happy.
哦 当然不了
Oh, he is not.
贝蒂依靠美国航空航天局的一个朋友知道
Betty leaned on someone at NASA.
解放组织解锁一颗卫星之后 又继续解锁其他卫星
Liber8 unlocked one satellite to get to another.
为了什么?
To what end?
嗯 弗门塔斯有一个服务器农场被称为黑欧宝
Well, Fermitas has an isolated server farm called Black Opal.
没有硬件线路的接入或接出
There's no hard lines in or out,
外部世界也无法接触到除非
there's no links to the outside world except...
除非用卫星
Via satellite.
真的是与世隔绝
So it's silo'd off from the world.
又一个保险箱
Another safety deposit box.
你应该早点告诉我们黑欧宝的事
You should have come clean about black opal.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
解放组织很聪明
Liber8 is clever.
如果不知道他们的目的我们是无法战胜他们的
You cannot fight them unless you know their end game.
他们拿到了什么?
What did they get?
警官们 你们今晚表现的很好
You did a great job here tonight, officers.
也许我们就把中间这些都跳过去
Maybe we should just skip to the end
也许他们可以开始叫我们保卫者了
maybe they can start calling us protectors.
你知道要不是贝蒂
You know we wouldn't have saved those hostages
我们救不了那些人质
if it hadn't have been for Betty.
她起了重要的作用
She made all the difference.
她让解放组织在这次交锋中占了上风
She made us play into Liber8's hands.
在她帮我们抓到那群混蛋之前
Until she helps us nail those bastards,
我是不会饶过她的
I can't look past that.
在电视上一通歇斯底里的咆哮
The terrorists won a small victory by getting
让他们取得了短暂的胜利
their delusional rant to air,
但是他们没有打倒任何人
but they did not defeat anyone.
有一个人应当得到我们所有人的尊敬
One man deserves credit
危急关头表现出最英勇的一面
for embodying the best that we can be.
那就是我们的警察局长杰克·狄龙
Inspector Jack Dillon.
他救了我 还有我的同事
He saved my life, and those of my colleagues.
为此 我将永远心存感激
And for that, I will be eternally grateful.
谢谢你 杰克
Thank you, Jack.
你的勇气鼓舞着我们
Your courage inspires us all.
看来有人爱上他了
I think someone has a bit of a crush.
是啊 他现在真的应该听点好消息
Yeah, he could use a little silver lining.
他已经听到了
He got that already.
昨天晚上有两个英雄 狄龙和你
There were two heroes last night, Dillon and you.
卡洛斯·福乃格 你是个优秀的指挥官
You are a leader of men, Carlos Fonnegra.
是啊 指挥别人
Yeah, men.
我是遵从你的命令引开他们的注意力的
I followed your orders to create that diversion.
也许你也不是那么差劲
Maybe there's a little hope for you after all.
妈妈会给我交保释的
Mom's gonna pay my bail.
我本来可以走的
I shouldn't even be here.
能让我和我女儿单独谈谈吗
Let me have a moment with my daughter.
让查普曼把录音器材关了
Tell Chapman to cut the recording.
好了 我们现在安全了
Ok, we're secure.
你胳膊怎么样?
How's your arm?
没事
It's nothing.
老爸 你还真是条汉子啊
You're so hardcore, dad.
你确定要这么做吗?
Are you sure about this?
后悔也来不及了
It's too late now.
不 还来得及
No, it's not.
老爸 木已成舟了
Dad, the course is set.
下一步怎么办?
So how's this gonna work?
我会动用我的关系对你轻判
I've used my influence to push for a lighter sentence.
三个月就行
Three months should do it.
你确定他们会来找我?
You sure they'll come for me?
负责追捕他们的家伙
Sympathetic daughter of the guy
却有一个富有同情心的女儿
in charge of catching them?
你就好像棒棒糖
You're like candy on a stick.
宝贝 你要让解放组织相信你支持他们的事业
Sweetheart, you make Liber8 believe you support their cause,
打入他们内部
you get inside,
你进去之后 我们将他们一网打尽
and once you're there we'll bring them down together.
他在电视上说的 有些我确实同意
What he said on that broadcast, I do agree with some of it.
那就好
That's good.
这样会保护你
It'll protect you if you believe it.
但是不要给弄出个派翠西亚·赫斯特 好吗?
Just don't go all Patty hearst on me, ok?
派翠西亚·赫斯特 美国报业大王威廉·赫斯特的孙女
但是不要给弄出个派翠西亚·赫斯特 好吗?
Just don't go all Patty hearst on me, ok?
1974年被绑架后加入激进组织并参与抢劫一家银行被FBI通缉
谁?
Who?
我知道她是谁 我不会的
I know who she is, I won't.
老爸 我相信你
I believe in you, dad.
好的
Ok.
我现在要走出去
I'm gonna walk out of here now.
你该大骂我一顿了
You should really let me have it.
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch!
我恨你 你听见了吗?
I hate you, you hear me?
我恨你!
I hate you!
你怎么能这样对我?!
How can you do this to me?!
你是怎么当父亲的?!!
What kind of a father are you?!!
这牺牲也太大了
That's a hell of a sacrifice.
做对的事是要付出代价的
Doing the right thing doesn't come cheap.
长官?
Sir?
她现在也许真的恨你 但是她还是你女儿
She may mean that now, but she is your child.
最终她会回到你的身边
In time you will get her back.
你又知道什么?
What do you know about it?
他们很快会来抓我的
They'll be coming for me soon.
但是我还是会再见到你的 对吗?
But I'm gonna see you again, right?
宝贝我爱你
I love you, baby.
人生有时你必须做出牺牲
Sometimes in life you've gotta make sacrifices.
但是你知道还有好的一面吗?
But you know the good thing?
就是我们可以一起做
We're doing this together.
这是能让你和你妈妈真正安全的方法
It's the only way you and mommy can truly be safe.
最终还是选择忠诚
Loyal after all.
你知道我们如何称呼那些帮助我们
Do you know what we call citizens
抓住恐怖分子的公民吗?
who help us apprehend terrorists?
不知道?
No?
爱国者
Patriots.
这个胸针会让所有人知道
This pin will let everyone know
你有多么的特别多么的忠诚
how special and loyal you truly are.
这标志着荣誉
It's a mark of honour.
你应该感到无比的骄傲
You should be very proud.
没关系的 宝贝
It's ok, baby.
没关系
It's ok.
你做的对
You did the right thing.